greevid.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy & Cookie - Greevid.com

Words used in the Greevid [Terms of Service](http://greevid.com/terms-of-service) (“Terms”) have the same meaning in this policy. Where there is any inconsistency between this Policy and those Terms, the Terms prevail.

### Your information we collect

#### Personal information

We keep the following personal information:

  * When a user signs up for particular services on our website they may need to give us the details required in our registration form and keep that information up to date;
  * Any personal information included in data uploaded to our system including but not limited to registration information.

We not keep records of IP addresses used to access our services.

Access to your data is by way of username and password and it is your responsibility to keep these safe and secure.

#### Non-personal information

We may also collect information about visits to our website to measure the number of visitors to different parts of the website, to assess user access patterns and otherwise to operate the website. We may use cookies or other similar technology for these purposes. By using our website or our services, you specifically agree to our use of cookies and such other technology to collect personal information. You can usually remove or block cookies (such as by using the settings in your browser), but it may affect your ability to use the website.

We may keep non-personal information about visits to the website or which is obtained via cookies or other similar technology:  
and might join that information with other users’ information and give it to advertisers in a way which doesn’t personally identify you;  
might analyse and use this information for marketing or statistical purposes as well as to improve the way we do business with our users.

#### Why we collect and store your personal information

We will collect keep personal information about users and other visitors to our site to provide services and support to them related to the website and our services, to sell services to them and also for dealing with other user activities, market and product research and to be able to give users promotional material on our other services and special offers.

#### How long we keep your information

We keep all your data and personal information while you are subscribed to our services but subject to our suspension and termination rights set out in our [Terms](http://greevid.com/terms-of-service).

#### Disclosure

If we think it is necessary or we have to by law in any jurisdiction then we are entitled to give your information to the authorities. We reserve the right to assist any law enforcement agency with investigations, including and limited to by way of disclosure of information to them or their agents. We also reserve the right to comply with any legal processes, including but not limited to subpoenas, search warrants and court orders. We may disclose your information to enforce or apply our [Terms](http://greevid.com/terms-of-service) or any other agreement we have with you; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of us or our other users or the operation of our services and the website.

We will not sell or otherwise provide your personal information to a third party other than our authorised resellers and service providers, or make any other use of personal information for any purpose which is not specifically allowed under this Policy or our [Terms](http://greevid.com/terms-of-service) or is not incidental to the normal use of our services.

We strongly urge you to use robust anti virus and firewall protection as we cannot guarantee the security of transmission from and to your computer over the Internet and thus cannot guarantee there will be no unauthorised access. Also, if you lose or otherwise allow access, you will lose the security of your data. In addition if you misplace or forget your username or password we have no ability to recover them for you, you will lose access to your data.

#### Communications

We may send bills, service updates and various other notices to you by email or using any internal messaging system we may provide as part of our service.

If appropriate, some of those notices will contain unsubscribe information so you can opt out of further receipt. We will abide by any e-mail unsubscription request (other than those we need to send you for billing, security or other service provider purposes).

#### Access to information

You can request access to all personal information we hold about you and correct it if it is wrong, in accordance with the USA/EU Privacy Act. To request any information we may be holding please contact our Privacy Officer by emailing [support@greevid.com](mailto:support@greevid.com). Any access request may be subject to a reasonable fee as permitted by law to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

#### Law

This Privacy Policy and its interpretation and operation are governed by all international law on the subject. You and we submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the USA/EU arbitral tribunals as further described in our Terms and you agree not to raise any jurisdictional issue if we need to enforce an arbitral award or judgment in USA/EU or another country.

#### Contact

Questions, comments or suggestions are welcome and should be directed to: [support@greevid.com](mailto:support@greevid.com).

#### Changes to our Policy

We may make changes to this Policy in the future. Any changes will be posted on website.  
Last updated May 2015

> Part of this policy and was taken out by the company “Mega Limited”
